Hello friends, my name is Sachin and
today I am back with a video for you to write. So
friends, today I am going to discuss with you the
Supreme Policy of SBI General Insurance. So friends, till now SBI used to
focus only on Arogya Plus policies because they were their best-
selling policies. If you want to know
how that policy is, then I will give
you the link here in the description and also on the i button,
you can see the policy.
But this policy has been
launched recently by SBI. Friends,
this policy has been
launched in three variants, that is, Pro.
If you want a policy of Rs 3 lakh to Rs 5 lakh, then
you can take its Pro plan.
If you want a policy of Rs 6 lakh to Rs 20 lakh, then
you will get its
Plus plan. And if you want a policy of Rs 25 lakh or
above, then
you will get the premium plan. Friends,
these are three parts of the same policy, but
I will give you separate videos for all three
so that you do not get confused because there are some more
facilities in Pro, some in Plus
and some for free.  And if I
tell you all the things in a single video, then
you will get confused somewhere or the other, that is why
I will
send you videos of Plus and Premium on this plan,
here you will also get their link on the i button
and their link will be found in the description, so you
can go there and see, so
friends, first of all our
product goes here, first of all we will
discuss it today, so see friends, there is a
problem here, today
we will know a little about it, first of all, in this
Someshwar is available, apart from that 3 lakh 4,
this 5 lakh, this 3 lakh 4, there are five
lucky policies, you can take it for free
and post-graduation friends, if we talk about it, then
here thirty days and directly, that is, these are
such expenses when you were not admitted in the hospital,
you had consulted the doctor, had done some
research, had bought some medicines, so these are the
expenses of this type, you
can get the discharge problem from the hospital from the company, in the same way, the
post ones are directly, that is, when you have been
discharged from the hospital and have come home
and after that you have consulted the doctor  If you have got some
medical tests done and taken some medicines, then
you will get the expenses for seven days here.
Talking about the room rent limit, friends,
here you get a single private air-conditioned room,
you can take a room here.
Talking about the ICU limit, friends, there is no
limit on the age limit here. The add-ons here, that is, the
charges for ICU, will be
presented to you here. No
action will be taken on this.
Look, talking about the treatment, friends,
these are such procedures that here you do
not need 24-hour hospitalization, that is,
you do
not need to stay in the hospital for more than 24 hours. If you went in the
morning, you came in the evening, or you got
admitted after a while, after four hours, after five hours, then here
you will get time in day care also.
These are about 500
such procedures. These surgeries are mostly done through these procedures,
as you must have seen that tractor
servicing takes some time. If you
take kidney stone surgery, then
that too takes some time.  If it goes, then such
parts which are included in the whole day treatment, let's
talk about no claim bonus,
friends, here
you will get a no claim bonus of fifteen percent every year, which will go up
to a maximum of hundred percent. Let's
talk about alternative treatment,
friends, as you must have seen that
Ayurveda, Siddha Unani, it is
also called AYUSH treatment, it is
available here, so you can take benefit from it here. Let's
talk about refilling benefit,
friends, that is, if suppose you have
taken a policy of Rs 5 lakh and Rs 5 lakh gets
exhausted in the same year, then the company
gives you Rs 5 lakh again here and
here friends, the best thing is that
here it gets activated with the first benefit, that
means, if suppose you have taken a
policy of Rs 5 lakh and the first benefit comes for Rs 2 lakh, then
now technically you have Rs 3 lakh benefit
and
in the refill, you have Rs 8 lakh plus 5
selected, total Rs 8 lakh left. If
any of your creams also costs up to Rs 8 lakh, then
it is passed here.  It will also
work if you meet through a love affair, but there should be a guest of 45 days in it. Let's move ahead
friends, now let's talk about
shoulder expenses friends, if suppose
someone ever
needs a kidney transplant or a liver
transplant, then here
any donor who has
donated his organ, his expenses are also
covered here. Now
talking about ambulance cover till God Sameshwar, friends,
here you will get an entry of ₹3000 for every hospitalization.
Talking about the entry age limit,
friends, any healthy person between 18 years to 65 years
can take this policy, but after 45 years, there is
a pre-policy checkup, that is, whether the
doctor talks to you on the phone or
you are sent to the center, a medical test is done here. In the
same way, suppose
you have taken this policy and you want to
add any new child born in your house, then
you can add the child here.  You can add 9120 in the
same way,
you can keep such dependent child up to 25 years in your policy, if we
talk about mission hospital operation, friends, then
that too is covered up to the main check, that is,
these are such expenses friends,
suppose the condition of the patient was not such that he could
go to the hospital and get treatment or he could
not be taken there or there is
no bed available in any nearby hospital, then
in such a condition, if
treatment is given at home for more than three days, here the
doctor is also available and does not visit your home,
so if this type of
hospitalization happens, then it is
called mission hospitalization, so its expenses are also covered
here till Sameshwar,
friends, if I talk about 108, then this
makes the policy very unique, if you
take any other policy, then HIV
and AIDS are covered up to a certain limit, it is
not covered completely, but
here, if there is HIV and AIDS, then at that
time  It is available till the end
but after taking this policy, if the disease will affect
you only at that time, if this
disease has already occurred and you take the policy later, then
you will not get this cover.
Friends, if we talk about psychiatry and cancer on maintenance, then it is covered here, now the entire time disease is covered, but there are
some such listed diseases here in
which you will be given 10 percent of it for the
time being. Suppose you have a
policy of Rs 4 lakh and here
its 10 percent is 40 thousand,
so here its limit is clearly
defined, it is 50 thousand maximum,
but in Chawla's policy it is 10 percent,
so here you will get only 40 thousand,
so see here it is written, on this occasion, let's
talk about listed conditions, genetic disorders, friends, these are the underlying conditions which go on from
generation to generation,
meaning any such disease which is passed on from your grandfather to
your father, from father to you,
now from you to your child, these are some such
diseases which keep running in the family, so in
this way  If there is any
problem which comes under genetic disorders,
here you will get coverage of up to Rs 1 lakh.
Now friends, let's talk about internal
congenital animal diseases. Friends, these are
such diseases which are born with birth,
meaning the
disease also came with your birth and whatever is there in it, it is on the
internal side, like suppose a hole in the heart
or any other such problem, then such
diseases will be covered here, but these
diseases will be covered only for Rs 25 per cent, by
squeezing them at this time, that is, if
you have a policy of Rs 5 lakh, then you will
get cover of such diseases up to Rs 1.25 lakh here.
Friends, some advanced treatments are also
covered here. Now, all the policies which are
not coming, all the friends are
covering advanced treatments as well, like
blue line plasty, oral
chemotherapy, robotic surgery,
stem cell therapy, so friends,
these are very advanced treatments which are being done in today's
date, so there is
coverage for that also here, but
I will leave the time for you to tell you about Rs 25 lakh.  Up to 100%.
If you have a policy of 4 lakhs, then
you can get treatment of up to 1 lakh rupees from here, whether it is 25% or not.
Friends, if we talk about help, then
it is available here, but you will get it
after the first year. They have network
diagnostic centers and you can go there and get
this test done. This is some list.
If you need English, you
can ask for it on WhatsApp or you
can also get it by emailing me. I will
give you complete information about it. Let's talk about eye surgery,
friends. So here it is a
surgery, friends.
Here your weight increases a lot
or obesity increases a lot and the
doctor suggests that you get it done,
otherwise you may get some other
diseases along with it. So such surgeries too,
friends, here you are covered for 10 minutes.
Talking about cataract cover, friends, then
that is also available here at 50 thousand rupees.
That means if you want to get both eyes done, then
you will get coverage of up to 1 lakh rupees,
but with that there
is a waiting period of two years for recovery.
Friends, if I talk about the benefit, then that
is also available here. Your hostel addition of ₹5000
means that if your hostel is more than a few rupees, then the
company also knows
that you must have incurred some extra
expenses here, like suppose your
relatives are coming and going,
your family members also come and go and
you have some expenses there, then keeping
this in mind, the company will give
you ₹5000 compensation benefit here.
Talking about air ambulance cover,
friends, it is not available here
because it is a best policy, it means it is not for a
long time and is not included in it, so
they have not included it in this grade plan.
You will get that cover in the plans above.
Talking about plan options, friends, here
you can take this plan as an individual, you
can take a family individual, meaning that the
owner of the same family is a member, there
are four members and they
want to be covered in a single policy certificate, then that too is covered.  You
can also avail this plan if you wish to avail this plan in a family floater scheme.
Suppose you have availed this plan for a period of time, then
three or four members of the family may avail this
plan. If you wish to avail this plan for
two years,
you can avail this plan with a discount of 4
%. If
you avail this plan for 30 days in one go,
you will get a discount of 6%.
Tax benefits are
also available here. This means that whoever purchases this plan will
get tax benefits under Section 80. Now, let me
tell you about the add-ons of this plan. These are the
basic features of this plan.
You
can also avail some add-ons as per your convenience. For this, you will have to do a
little bit of
your choosing. Friends,
how about Hospital Delhi? Suppose you have a hospital stay of
4 days or a hospital stay of 5
days, and
if you have availed this hospital cash there.
So suppose you have an option here,
like if there is a 5 day pollution
then you can take a plan of ₹500 also, now you can
also use a plan of Rs.1000, this can be clarified as
well, 5,000, if you had
taken a 10 day, 15 day or 45 day plan here, let's take an
example in this combination that you had
taken a 10 day plan and had
taken a plan of ₹1000, then here if you are getting a 10 day
hostel scan, then
you will get ₹5,000 which is a benefit with the plan, along with that
you will
get ₹10000 extra here, you will get it
in reimbursement mode because you have paid extra money for this,
friends, talking about the major relief benefit, here the
piece is listed in the same way, under which
you get any disease or use, then
whatever was
left at that time will be given to you in full, that is,
suppose you had taken this policy of 5 lakhs
and someone gets cancer, this is  That is meter
surgery which is part of that list
and if suppose he is Bigg Boss
then you have to
share the diagnosis report with the company and ₹5 will be
deposited in your account. You will get the treatment
expenses that you were getting. This
overage is now a benefit but if you take its
updated plan, if you take any massage 40-50
lata plan then there also you will
get maximum coverage of only up to 25 lakh rupees, that is, under this plan and you have
taken 5 lakhs then you will get full coverage of 5 lakhs.
Friends, here
apart from extras there is an option for accident performance, that
means if there is
hospitalization due to an accident then here your
policy can work for Rs 7.5 lakhs instead of 5 lakhs
and up to 10 lakhs,
that is you
can increase your policy up to two times in case of hospitalization. Yes, this is an
option, if you make a search then the
premium will be charged at one and a half times.
Now if you want to increase it by double then
this year's premium will be charged at double times.
Friends, many people  It seems
that the little one
or no claim bonus that you are getting today is very less, it is
15 per cent, which is very less, so
friends, you can save a little extra money, you can
change it here, you can change it up
to 25 percent, which was earlier
going up to 15 per cent of hundred percent, now by increasing
it by 25 percent every year,
this maximum of the big one will go up to 200 percent, that is,
earlier if you had taken a policy of 5 lakhs, then the
25 percent of 5 lakhs is
yours, then by doing this your policy will keep getting added
and this 5 lakh will
go up to Rs 1000000, that is, the total policy of whatever
you have, this amount will become up to Rs 1500000,
if you have not taken any claim, so
friends, here there is also a protector of no claim bonus,
if suppose any of your
friends
lives below 50 rupees and you had
taken this protector like this, then the no
claim bonus that you were supposed to get will definitely be given, that is your
no  Claim bonus will not be deducted. Pent option
is available friends because here there is 10
percent and 20 percent. I would suggest you
not to take it because if you also
take this option then your premium will be reduced
here but if ever any claim comes then
whatever option you had taken of 10 percent or
Beech Hussain, you will have to pay
10 percent or 20 percent of your hospital bill from your pocket. There
is an option by updating any room friends that if you have taken a
policy of Rs. 5 here, this minimum ₹5 is
not available on torture, then you have left aside the
category of suite or above and
asked that you
get deluxe room, super deluxe, then
that can also be turned off here because
in your policy till now
I will do single category that you will get single private,
you will take this money, that means
you will take this donut and if you spend a little money
then you will be
able to update the upper room also friends, there
is a deductible option here too, if you consider that many
people say that we want to reduce our premium
and  But if any hospital bill
comes, we have enough money to pay Rs. 10,000 or Rs. 25,000
from our profit,
so friends, your premium here will be
reduced to a great extent, but
whenever any bill comes within the year, the first bill of Rs.
10,000 or Rs. 25,000, whichever option you choose,
you will have to pay from your pocket,
this is just an option to reduce the exam,
you can choose as per your convenience, let's move ahead
friends, I will
tell you that I am on Facebook, on Twitter or
we have created a group for you,
you can also add me on Telegram here, here you will find the
latest information about insurance, if there are any
changes in any plane, if any new plane has
come or you want to ask me any questions,
my WhatsApp number is here, if you
want to write me an email, my email is here,
Sachin, on penalty corner, you can ask me, so
friends, these are all my dead cells,
you can connect with it, let's move ahead
friends, now let's talk about your ghee,
friends, there are explosions which
you get inside this plant  In this situation, they will
not give less. Suppose you had any pre-existing
disease, suppose you had
Ashwagandha, BP, Thyroid, Cholesterol, then
friends, if you have any such old problem which
you had before taking the policy, then there will be a
waiting period of 4 years here.
Only after 4 years will your problem be
covered. Friends, here there will be a
waiting period of 2 years for you, such as
cataract, hernia, joint
replacement, stones, sinus,
nasal polyp, or you have some other
problem related to the tumor.
Friends, whatever such problem is there, it is like this
in almost all the policies and here
also it is like this, after about 2 years your
disease will be covered because these are some
things. Friends, there is a waiting period of 30 days
because in other policies you will get that the
accident cover here is
Devan Shweta ready, that is, accident
cover which you can take half-heartedly, but
you will not get cover for any disease for the first three days.
Friends, there is a waiting period of 90s here, in
which there is hypertension, that is,
problems related to BP, heart
disease, diabetes-related complications,
if any such claim comes within the first 90 days, then
you will not get it only after a long time, for
these diseases, the
waiting period of Nirjan Ras benefit of these 3Ds, which I
told you that you will get lump sum money together,
so here it will start for you only after ₹90
and the survival period is of 30 days
or not, if suppose you have a
major disease like cancer
or you have kidney failure, then friends,
here survival means
you have to subscribe to that disease for 30 days, that
means death should not happen for 30 days, if this is the case then
you will get this benefit, if we
talk about the combination of this, friends, then this is a
15-day waiting period for vinegar,
after this, after 15 days,
you should also get treatment with vinegar.  You can avail more benefits
after taking this policy.
If you want more details about it, then
you can read its policy details.
I will give you the link in the description, you
can download the policy details there. I will give you the details of how to buy this policy
in the description, so by
going there you can see all these things. So
friends, I hope you have understood some plan.
If you liked the plan, then do
not forget to share it with your friends.
If you are new to my channel, then do not forget to
subscribe to it. My name is
Sachin Verma. I will meet you
in the next video. Thank you very much for watching this video.